Jose Rodriguez Vizcaino

Frontend Web developer

Barranquilla, Colombia (GMT-5) (+57) 301 295 5636 jo.sed10@hotmail.com https://wa.me/573012955636 https://linkedin.com/in/jrvizcaino https://jrodrigu3.github.io/

Web developer with +3 years of experience developing web applications using (Angular 8 - 14 .Net, and Node.js). I have worked in the private and public sectors on human resources projects, accounting projects, private and public transportation, and health. I feel my greatest contribution to a project is the ability to communicate with other team members in order to improve the web page functionalities, as well as identify performance improvements on the projects. I am driven by innovation, being able to teach my knowledge, learn new things, and take on new challenges.

EXPERIENCE

ConsWare, Full-Stack Developer (Outsourcing company) — OCT, 2021 – NOV 2022

- I led a team where we designed a vehicle policy program, improving the user experience by 25%.
- We designed a credit program for vehicles, improving the user experience by 45% by applying good coding practices.
- Contributed with the BackEnd team to improve the JSON responses and save the time of its implementation in Frontend by 50% by applying good coding practices and improving the structure.
- I designed a dynamic information mail-sending control. Tech

Stack: Angular, Redux, .Net, SQL Server, HTML5 and CSS3.

<u>DigitalWare</u> (Direct customer) **CHATBOT**

— JUN, 2021 – OCT, 2021

- I led a team where we developed and implemented, free of charge, a chatbot that saves 100% on the cost of the Azure chatbot service.
- We designed a website to generate questions and their respective answer for the chatbot, improving user searchtime by 60%.
- Free implementations of the chatbot in a productive environment, reducing the external expenses, of thecompany.

Tech Stack: Angular, .Net, Express, SQL Server, HTML5, and CSS3.

Occupational health — APR, 2021 - JUN, 2021

- We designed a patient entry module.
- I designed a satisfaction survey program.
- Promote the best organization of the project by 25% through the use of Scrum, which allowed us to better define the
 objectives.

Tech Stack: Angular, .Net, HTML5 and CSS3.

SAQ, Web Developer (Outsourcing company) — OCT, 2020 - APR, 2021

- Improved webpage access by 25%.
- Reduced the number of bugs reported in a website by the client by 50% with good communication with the customer.
- Collaboration with the Backend team for the creation of new APIs.

Tech Stack: Angular, PHP, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, Jquery - ajax, SQL Server, HTML5, and CSS3.

CompExpress, Junior Developer (Direct customer) — JUN, 2018 – APR, 2020

- planned, coordinated, and executed preventive and corrective maintenance.
- We designed software that was developed to control product sales.
- Submit maintenance reports.
- Test custom system.
- 3D modeling.

Tech Stack: PHP, MySql, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Advanced: JavaScript, TypeScript, C#; Intermediate: Java, C; Basic: Python, Dark.

Frameworks Tools: Advanced: Angular, .Net; Intermediate: Express, Jquery, SQL Server management studio; Basic: Android studio, Flutter.

Data Base: Advanced: SQL Server, PostgreSQL; Intermediate: MySQL; Basic: MongoDB.

Tools: Git, Slack, Azure, Azure Devops.

Agile: SCRUM

Languages: Intermediate: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

University Name - Barranquilla, Colombia. Electronic Engineer, Sep 2018